also Traverse the road
um that trust building exercise is what
is what makes that that social apoptosis
so difficult that fact that we give so
much emotion to the decisions we make
and it's it's hard to say you're wrong
it's hard even in academics that's why
it's sort of incentivized it's like it's
an honorous state to find you know
extract your error and declare it in the
real world you know people have to trust
that you are building a system of
success and if you place doubt on that
if you break away the Integrity of your
or science or however you build your
machines maybe people won't be clapping
for you and for that simple reason I
think um I don't speak out as much I
think for those simple reasons you may
not speak out whether we're again
talking about relationships workplace or
Nation or your internal monologue this
idea of knowing when it's the right time
to kill your cells to perform the
apoptosis of your own thoughts is kind
of the big idea I want to know what dumb
ideas I'm still following and I bet you
want to know what dumb ideas you're